freejobalert.in 2014-03-31

# Privacy Policy | Freejobalert.in

**Privacy Policy for the website: www.freejobalert.in**  
We are always committed to safeguard your Personal Information. In this regard with Privacy Statement which governs and make the use of your personal information such as email address. Some of this information provided by you is used for our own legitimate business purposes, such as sending you latest govt. jobs updates of the other event happening on our website and is not shared or use for the benefit of any non-affiliated third-party.

**Disclaimer** :  
This is in concerning to our visitor’s, who visit the website www.freejobalert.in to collect the information about jobs and vacancies in Government and Privets Sectors. We collect employment news info from various sources and the same is provided to the user for the informational purpose. Visitors are the responsible to crosses check validity and other information/ requirements in regards of jobs of his/her interest from the official website of the organisation. This web portal provides information on jobs opening in various government organisations and for more exact information on government jobs or any other employment notice which is displayed on the www.freejobalert.in has to be verified by the applicant from the official website of given source. We provide the information at the best of our knowledge, and to be safer side same has to be verified by the individuals, from the given source of link/ or the other employment medium provided. www.freejobalert.in is not responsible for any type of loss or damaged happen to the individual with the given jobs information.

**Use of Information** :  
We would also like to inform you that, the www.freejobalert.in make the use of logfile to track the information of users ip address, date/ time of visit and demographic information etc., which is use to analysis the trends for our users who are looking for the government employments or other privet jobs. We also serve the third-party advertisement service, like google adsence, infolink etc. These third-party ad servers or advt. networks use latest technology for publish the advertisements, This technology may use cookies and web beacons on our site to measure the relativeness and effectiveness of their advertisements or to personalize the advertising content that you see. We have no control over the cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. If you required any more information, for this you have to consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad service providers.

**Copyright** :  
All the content of www.freejobalert.in is copyright protected hence no other website are can reproduce the full content without taking prior permission from us. But you are always free to make a use of summery of the publish content ie. 2 to 3 lines along with anchor text/ hyperlink pointing to www.freejobalert.in for reading the full content.

If you have any questions or queries in regard with our website then please feel free to contact us.
